I met my first client today.
Her name is Lain; she's 12 years old.
When Professor Takashima assigned her to me,
I was frustrated that he gave me a such a young client,
since she's way out of the age range I specialize in.
But, as soon as I saw her face, I felt at ease.
Was it because she was so adorable?
Hmmm.
There was something oddly compelling about her.
Anyway, within my age range or not, she's still my client.
She seems to be experiencing extreme psychosis, and some level of mental instability.
Is she be having trouble at home?
Perhaps her childhood experiences have severely warped her self image.
I hope I can help her.
Little by little, I'll get her to open up more.
I can't rush it.