Do you know where I'm going?
I don't know either,
because I'm about to be born.
Is that an evolved human being?
You can think that if you want.
Don't you need a body to to be a human?
Some people have bodies that aren't necessarily human.
And me?
Am I not human?
Lain is Lain.
What does it mean to be human?
If I have a body, does that make me human?
I am me.
Are you trying to blend in?
You need a body if you're going to live in the real world.
Suicide would be stupid.
You're better off dead.
Don't I need my body?
What if I need it someday?
I'm not sure.
But you don't need a body to live in the Wired.
I'll need the memories of a body.
What about the memories of an aging body?
What if my beliefs change?
Do they need to change?
There's no guarantee it's you.
Hey, Lain, what do I need to get on the Wired?
Will and existence.
The rest is just data.