I met Lain for the second time today.
She looked straight at me and called me "Doctor."
It made me so happy, that my face turned bright red.
Maybe she's already figured me out.
If I get flustered just from being called "Doctor",
It's easy to tell that I'm pretty inexperienced...
But, I still get that weird feeling that I got when we first met.
I can't seem to place it.
When I look in her eyes,
it feels like she can see right through me.
Do I look unreliable to her?
Even so, I wish I was that calm when I was her age.
I wouldn't quite call her an elegant girl,
but it's safe to say she seems pretty relaxed.
I thought she'd be acting like a child,
but she really feels like an adult.
Well, they do say kids grow up pretty quick these days.
Lots of my relatives' kids are mature for their age too.
Times are changing, huh?
Ahhh, I'm starting to talk like an old woman!
Don't let your hallucinations get to you, Lain!
I'll help you get better, I promise.