According to the client's mother, she has frequent nightmares.
But, they're far from ordinary nightmares.
They're much more realistic, almost hallucinatory in nature.
It seems they're the reason she started counselling.
As for the nightmares, Lain typically doesn't elaborate on their contents,
but she says she hears cryptic voices, or that her eyes are forced open, as she's shown what seems like a video.
Or even she'll be playing in the garden with friends, and before she realizes, she's suddenly alone.
As of now, these seem to be the product of normal childhood fears.
To think that these symptoms will fade as she finds her sense of self,
well, it's certainly optimistic,
but based on other clinical studies with children, I think it's quite likely.
Her answers were clear, and she seemed to be present enough that even if symptoms continued,
the client would more than likely be able to live a normal life.
However, what concerns me the most, are the hallucinations her mother had mentioned.
It's very unusual for a child her age to be experiencing these symptoms.
The most important issue is to determine what's causing these delusions and hallucinations.
I'll have to determine this through our counselling sessions.