8th of July, 2 p.m., 2nd session.
Please come in.
Dr. Touko, hello.
Hello, Lain!
Hello.
Summer vacation is coming up!
Are you excited?
Not especially.
Let's see...
Let's play a game today, Lain! I brought this with me.
What’s that?
They're art supplies.
Do you like to draw?
Not really...
Probably not.
I see... unfortunate.
Wait - do you know tic-tac-toe?
I know what it is, but I don't really want to play right now.
I’m sorry.
I'm all out of ideas.
Is there anything you'd like to do, Lain?
I’d like to talk some more.
Talk...
Talk about what?
Anything is fine.
Let's talk about you.
About me?
I'm not really that interesting...
Is that a no?
No, not at all.
But, I'm 27 years old.
There'd be way too much to talk about!
We'd have to start from the beginning, and it's a long story.
Honestly, I don't really have anything interesting to say!
What kind of doctor are you?
Kind of doctor? Well,
I help people like you, who have things they're worried about.
And then I help them understand what they can do to fix it.
Make sense?
Ah...
I knew it.
What’s wrong?
If I'm making you uncomfortable, let me know. You can be honest with me.
I should be more careful, really.
You shouldn’t worry so much.
Just relax, and come have a nice talk with me once a month.
Okay...