Is there a variety of milk as well?
Yep! They're practically all the same.
The different types are just based on how they're processed.
Different types?
It's like tea - it can be wildly different based on how the leaves are picked and steeped.
Even if you use the same leaves.
People, too?
Hmm?
Are there different types of people?
Not really types, but everybody varies from person to person.
For example, you don’t like tea, but I really like it.
Or like how some people get upset stomachs from milk, while some don't, right?
Some people can even get used to drinking milk when they're older, like me.
Even you might learn to like tea one day, right?
It doesn't have to be good or bad,
things just naturally vary from person to person.
Don't worry if you're different,
really, you should be proud of it!
Proud?
I’m sorry...
That’s right, you're troubled, aren't you?
You don't have to boast about it or anything,
but I meant more that you shouldn't worry about what others think.
Am I different for having strange dreams?
It could be different, but it could also be totally normal.
That's what I'm here for - if you're worried, I want to help you with it.
Not to help you stop having those dreams,
but rather helping you to explain things you don’t understand.
I'm more than happy to talk to you about anything that's bothering you.
I’ve studied a lot to help you with this kinda thing.
I’m still studying, actually.
If you’re ever in trouble, don't be afraid to come talk with me.
I’d like to know more about you, Lain.
Is that okay?
Wonderful!
Starting today, let's be friends.
You better visit!
Promise?
I want to learn about you, too!
You can ask me anything you want.
We'll look up anything you don't understand.
I'll even make sure to get your favorite drink.
What?
Milk that doesn’t make your stomach rumble!