Touko? If I really *am* sick, what do we do?
If you're sick?
If... you know.
Since you're so young, and your symptoms are relatively minor, I wouldn't want to use medicine to treat you.
Why not?
Lain, your body can already recover from sickness quite well.
But depending on medicines will weaken your body's ability to recover on its own.
Children especially shouldn't rely too heavily on medication.
So what are you going to do?
We can use psychotherapy - like how we're talking now.
Only talking?
It's hard to explain. For example, we have a program for recovering alcoholics.
Everyone shares stories, and discusses what led them to developing their drinking habits.
It's called group therapy - but, I don't think it really works.
Why not?
I don't think people who use the persuasion of others to fuel their recovery tend to stay on the right track.
They feel as if they've recovered fully, but once they're alone again they lose the momentum and fall back on old habits.
I've seen a lot of people like that.
Then what do we do instead?
I'd rather work with someone one on one - like we're doing now, Lain.
And?
And then, I encourage my patients to reflect on themselves.
Non-directive psychotherapy. Instead of giving the patient specific instructions, I try to analyze them from a more neutral ground.
This makes it easier for them to look at themselves and recognize what's wrong, so they can work towards recovery with the help of their doctor.
They learn how to heal on their own.
When they can do that, that's when they're truly cured.
Is it really that easy to get better?
It sounds easy. However...
The truth is, it's incredibly difficult.
Difficult?
(yawning) Sorry - I haven't been getting enough sleep.
You're tired. Shouldn't you get a little more rest?